Christolin Michel

Junior Web Developer

Personal Info

Address

210 East 51st

Brooklyn NY, 11203

Apt B5

Phone

1 (718) 576 8388

E-mail

ChristolinM@ymail.com

Portfolio Website

http://MichelC.Design/

Development Skills

HTML & CSS

advanced

Java Script

JQuery

Java

Swift (MacOS, iOS Development)

In progress

PHP

Other Skills

Customer Service

Expert

Video Editing

Photoshop/GIMP

IT Technical knowledge

Web Developer with 2+ years of Multimedia experience.

Areas of concentration include Visual Communication, Client Relations and Image Manipulation.

Innovation oriented and eager blend new techniques with popular frameworks and libraries to achieve the client's desired results.

My goal is to build with a company that can benefit from my interpersonal skills and strategic mindset; a position where I can provide an efficient and streamlined environment for both internal and external customers.

Experience

2017-06 - Front End Web Development Intern

2017-09

Industry City, Innovation Lab

Responsibilities:

- · Lead Developer of team protects
- Designed Responsive Websites for local businesses within the Brooklyn,
 Sunset Park area
- · Presented finished site designs to company board members and directors
- Earned Adobe Creative Cloud Certification
- · Completed three months of an intensive web developer boot camp

2017-09 - Flexible Engineer

present

Flexible Business Systems

Responsibilities:

- Back-End/Server Support
- Remote/Onsite Desktop Support
- Maintained Company/Client Relations
- · Studied for CompTIA Network+ Certification

2014-08 - IT Lead Technician

2017-06

Stony Brook University

Responsibilities:

- · Trained Students, Interns and Helpdesk personnel
- Supported end users with issues pertaining to Google's Educational Suite,
 Office 365, Windows, Mac, and various flavors of Linux
- · System Image Management/Deployment

Additional Activities

2006-06 - Developer/ICON Artist

2012-06

BYOND (Hobby)

Responsibilities:

- · Manipulated game files and images to fit program requirements
- Tested Game mechanics and Logic Prior to launches
- · Created 3D renders of characters using Ani8tor
- · Created detailed Pixel art
- · Created game sounds using WMM & Garage Band

Education

2012-06 Stony Brook University, Technical Systems Management w/ Concentration in Computer Science BS

Completing BS in TSM - 2019